<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<info>
    <id>files_reader</id>
    <name>Reader (ebook reader)</name>
    <namespace>Files_Reader</namespace>
    <summary>An epub-compatible ebook reader based on a pure javascript epub renderer</summary>
    <description>
	Reader is an ebook reader based on pure javascript renderers. It works for books formatted according to the epub standard as well as those conforming to the (informal) CBR and CBZ ('comics') scheme.

	For Epub Reader uses the futurepress epub.js renderer (https://github.com/futurepress/epub.js) to provide near-native looks, especially when used full-screen. Turn pages by pressing the left/right hand side of the screen/window or using the cursor keys (if you have those), use the sidebar to browse through chapters or bookmarks and add annotations.

	CBR and CBZ are supported using a custom renderer based in part on balaclark's work (https://github.com/balaclark/HTML5-Comic-Book-Reader). As with Epub, books can be navigated using the keyboard as well as mouse or touch navigation.

	For text-based formats Reader has a night mode (toggled by clicking or pressing the book title/author on top of the viewer) to read in the dark without waking up the neighbours. This is obviously most effective when used full-screen. The colours used for night mode are configurable in the Settings dialog.

	Also in Settings you'll find the option to use ignore any internal formatting in the book by forcing a given font style and size.

	Current reading position and settings are saved to the server which makes it possible to start reading on one device and continue on another without losing track of where you were.
    </description>
    <version>0.8.4</version>
    <licence>AGPL</licence>
    <author>Frank de Lange</author>
    <documentation>
        <user>https://github.com/Yetangitu/owncloud-apps/blob/master/files_reader/README.md</user>
    </documentation>
    <bugs>https://github.com/Yetangitu/owncloud-apps/issues</bugs>
    <website>https://github.com/Yetangitu/owncloud-apps/files_reader</website>
    <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Yetangitu/owncloud-apps/master/screenshots/files_reader-1.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Yetangitu/owncloud-apps/master/screenshots/files_reader-2.png</screenshot>
    <screenshot>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/Yetangitu/owncloud-apps/master/screenshots/files_reader-3.png</screenshot>
    <category>files</category>
    <category>multimedia</category>
    <category>office</category>
    <dependencies>
        <owncloud min-version="8.1" max-version="9.2" />
        <nextcloud min-version="8.1" max-version="12"/>
		<database>pgsql</database>
		<database>sqlite</database>
		<database>mysql</database>
    </dependencies>
    <ocsid>167127</ocsid>
</info>
